let's start off by talking about the
mountains do you like to go on holiday
in the mountains definitely it's one of
my favorite things to do I actually love
nature and um the mountains specifically
like I always handpick locations which
have mountains and like a beautiful
landscape Greenery and uh I love hiking
as well so that's why are there any
hotels in the mountains in your country
Yes actually uh in Himel they have
lodges they rent it out to people who
are there on vacations and uh it's the
most beautiful experience because you
get to actually see how people who are
uh based there how they live and how
they cook and how they clean and you get
the whole experience of everything now
let's talk about trees do you like trees
yeah actually I love trees I love
spending time around trees when I look
at a tree I feel um very alive uh
because there's just so much history
that goes with it I mean um especially
like you get oxygen so when you just sit
there and meditate it's like the best
feeling in the world you feel very
refreshed as well are there many trees
around your hometown there are but not
so much uh as of now because it's mostly
City and buildings and shops um but I
would love for it to be what are the
benefits of planting more trees there
are only benefits of planting more tree
I mean it protects you from so many
things and uh it's so much better for
your health to have trees around you
also um I think for Plantation um even
for food and stuff like uh to get fresh
fruits and vegetables you can always
have it available outside of your home
if you just have like those planted
trees around you now let's talk about
the weather what time of year did you
enjoy the most when you were a child I
would definitely say November December
so like towards the end of the year and
when winter arrives or even during
September October when it's rainy season
season I enjoy myself the most I think
because I love when it's cold and chilly
and you can just go out for a walk or
play outside with your friends I think
that's when I enjoy it the most has the
weather changed much in recent years I
would say drastically yes um it's gotten
hotter and hotter and humid I think
because of global warming it's been
really bad lately would you say the
weather in your hometown is suitable for
working I mean around December yes but
throughout the year no it's very very
hot back in India it's like um when you
get out it's a lot of um humidity and
you just don't feel your best the TV
documentary that I watched was a
documentary on uh the artist Eminem um
he goes by the name Marshall mats and uh
I remember I was very young when I
watched it and um the reason I love it
is because it's very inspiring because
in the movie he he shows all of his
struggles and the poverty that he went
through when he was very unfortunate as
a child and even when he was a teenager
and that goes to show how much
determination he had towards his dreams
and his plans and goals of the future
that he knew that he was going to make
it big in the music industry and now
he's known to be one of the biggest
musical artists in the industry I
learned inspiration from that movie I
think it gives you a lot of motivation
every time you watch it it goes to show
that you know no matter what no matter
where you come from no matter how small
your hometown was or how many obstacles
you had in life but still you can make
it big and um it also goes to show that
you just have to be passionate about
what it is that you want in your life
and through that you can achieve the
greatest things and you can surpass even
your highest levels of insecurities and
doubts that you have and the fears that
you have and he's also like one of my
favorite artist
so to see him go through that really
inspires you and shows you that you can
do it no matter what it is that it's
usually self-doubt which keeps you um
from chasing your dreams or from
achieving your goals but in that movie
it's shown that um you can really do
whatever you want so we've been talking
about a TV documentary that you watched
and we're going to continue to talk
about TV programs and TV advertising do
you think that there are too many game
shows on TV nowadays
um to thank you for watching this video
I want to give you a free course that
has helped thousands of students improve
their I speaking score what it's going
to do is take you through every single
part of the test and give you strategies
for part one part two and part three and
also allow you to practice at home for
free and get feedback to sign up for
that for free all you have to do is just
click the link in the description thanks
very much and let's get back to the
video I don't think so no I think um
there's enough for everyone so I think
there is a lot of different genres that
uh people can watch and game shows are
mostly educational so I think uh that's
also very necessary in today's
generation and to remind everyone to
have fun and not take life so seriously
is TV the main way people get news in
your country yes for sure I would agree
I mean um it's one of the most important
Outlets from where people can know
what's going on like the breaking news
or what happened yesterday everyone's
always aware now let's talk about TV
advertising what kind of products are
advertised most often on TV um I would
say mostly Home Products like cleaning
products or uh soaps or maybe beauty
products are mostly what's advertised or
also electronic appliances are are very
much advertised in my country do you
think that people pay attention to
adverts on
TV to thank you for making it this far
in the video I want to give you 10% off
our VIP course I VIP course is the most
successful I course in the world that is
a fact because we have more band seven
eight and nine success stories than any
other I course in the entire world we do
that by simplifying the whole I process
supporting you with some of the best is
teachers in the world and being with you
every step of the way until you get the
score that you need all you have to do
is just look down in the description
just click that and you can sign up if
you have any questions about the VIP
course always feel free to get in touch
with us we answer 100% of the questions
that we get hope that you become a VIP
if not enjoy the rest of this free video
not as much as they used to because back
then it was a form of entertainment but
now they just want to skip and uh Reach
the the show that they're watching it's
not as much as it used to be I think
people grew impatient now they're not as
patient as they used to be because um of
the fast-paced life everyone's going
through so they want everything quick
how important are regulations on TV
advertising I think they are very
important and uh there should be
regulations but at the same time I think
that it's not followed as much as it it
should be that's the end of the speaking
test while done thank you